<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item>
	<title>Phixel | LinkedIn 💼
Our Professional Side</title>
	<content>Welcome to The Phixel's LinkedIn page, where we share our latest design projects, industry insights, and career opportunities with our professional network. We believe in the power of design to create meaningful and impactful experiences, and we're passionate about connecting with like-minded professionals in the industry. Follow us today and join our network!

Thank you for connecting with The Phixel on LinkedIn. We're excited to have you join our professional network and share our passion for design. Be sure to follow us to stay up-to-date with our latest projects, industry insights, and career opportunities. Let's explore the possibilities of design together!</content>
	<excerpt>Join the design revolution with Phixel on LinkedIn. Follow us for exclusive career opportunities and stay ahead of the game.</excerpt>
	<description>Are you ready to join the design revolution and take your career to the next level? Look no further than Phixel on LinkedIn. We're not your average design agency - we're dynamic, innovative, and fiercely passionate about creating engaging and memorable experiences for our clients. When you follow us on LinkedIn, you'll gain access to exclusive career opportunities and stay ahead of the game with our industry insights and latest projects. We believe in the power of design to inspire and delight, and we're excited to connect with like-minded professionals who share our passion. So why wait? Join our professional network today and let's explore the possibilities of design together.</description>
	<media>
		<url type="">media/f2706672/a</url>
	</media>
	<info>
		<slug>linkedin</slug>
		<date>01/01/2020</date>
		<url>https://linkedin.com/company/the-phixel/</url>
		<short>https://bit.ly/3kPhClN</short>
		<category>External</category>
		<url>external</url>
		<emojis>🎨👥🌟🚀💼📈📢</emojis>
		<hashtags>
			<hashtag>Design</hashtag>
			<hashtag>ProfessionalNetwork</hashtag>
			<hashtag>LinkedIn</hashtag>
			<hashtag>Industry</hashtag>
			<hashtag>Career</hashtag>
			<hashtag>Inspiration</hashtag>
		</hashtags>
		<tags>
			<tag>Design</tag>
			<tag>Professional Network</tag>
			<tag>LinkedIn</tag>
			<tag>Industry</tag>
			<tag>Career</tag>
			<tag>Inspiration</tag>
		</tags>
	</info>
</item>
