<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item>
	<title>Referral Rewards Program - Make some serious cash! 💰</title>
	<content>#### Do you know someone who needs a digital solution for their business? Why not earn some extra cash while helping them out?

### Introducing Phixel's Referral Rewards Program!

As a specialized team of designers and developers, we provide personalized and unique digital solutions for businesses of all sizes.

We’ve worked with some well-known brands and are always eager to take on new challenges.

### Earn **5%** to **15%** with this Amazing Opportunity!

With our Referral Rewards Program, you can earn a commission ranging from **5%** to **15%** of the project’s value just by referring clients to us. The commission rate depends on the industry, the size of the business, and the value of the client. It’s an easy and hassle-free way to earn some extra money.

## Program tiers

### **15%** if less than $1K

#### Individuals & Professionals projects or less than $1, 000 USD

Dominate your game and earn a 15% commission on every digital solution project you refer that’s worth less than $1, 000.

Help your friends and colleagues elevate their personal brand or professional services, while making some extra cash!

### **12%** if less than $2K

#### Products or Services projects between $1, 000 and $2, 000 USD

Step up your game and earn a 12% commission on every digital solution project you refer that's worth between $1, 000 and $2, 000.

Help your friends and colleagues dominate their market and elevate their products or services, while making some sweet cash!

### ***10%** if less than $3K
#### Starting Businesses projects between $2, 000 and $3, 000 USD

Start strong and earn a 10% commission on every digital solution project you refer that’s worth between $2, 000 and $3, 000.

Help your friends and colleagues kick-start their new business venture and become a badass entrepreneur, while making some cool cash!

### ***7%** if less than $5K
#### Small Businesses projects between $3, 000 and $5, 000 USD

Raise the bar and earn a 7% commission on every digital solution project you refer that’s worth between $3, 000 and $5, 000.

Help your friends and colleagues level up their small business game and become awesome in their industry, while making some deserved cash!

### ***5%** if less than $10K
#### Medium Businesses projects between $5, 000 and $10, 000 USD

Accelerate your growth and earn a 5% commission on every digital solution project you refer that’s worth between $5, 000 and $10, 000.

Help your friends and colleagues scale up their medium-sized business and become a badass in their industry, while making some well-deserved cash!

### ***Negotiable** if over $15K
#### Large Businesses projects over $15, 000 USD

Challenge yourself and negotiate your commission rate for every digital solution project you refer that’s worth over $15, 000.

Help your friends and colleagues take their large business to the next level and become a badass leader in their industry, while making some sweet cash!

**Note:** Provided rates and percentages are for reference only and subject to change depending on factors such as client size, project difficulty, and other variables. These rates and fees may be negotiable, and each project will be evaluated on an individual basis to determine the appropriate budget.

### Lear more about us:

| [Clients](https://phixel.net/en/about-us/clients/) | [Services](https://phixel.net/en/about-us/services/) |
|-|-|
## Ready for Take Off?

#### Don't miss out on this opportunity to earn while helping!

At Phixel, we love to share our knowledge and expertise while helping others shape their ideas. Contact us today to learn more about our services and referral program.

### You can reach us through

| [phixel.net](https://phixel.net/) | [contact@phixel.net](mailto:contact@phixel.net) | [(+57) 312 583 7936](https://web.whatsapp.com/send/?phone=+573125837936) |
|-|-|-|

#### We're always happy to answer any questions you may have.

### Disclaimer

- This commission applies only to the first project with a specific client.
- The payment of the commission is subject to the client's prompt payment for the project.
- You cannot interfere with the client's negotiations or the project itself.
- You cannot be the same client or bussines partner as the owner of the project.
- The price of the project is confidential, and is subject to change; it will only be shared with you in agreement with the client.
- Any negotiations or agreements regarding commission rates must be made in writing and agreed upon by both parties.
- We reserve the right to refuse or terminate any commission agreement at our discretion.
- We are not liable for any damages or losses resulting from any commission agreement or referral of any digital solution projects.
- By participating in our commission program, you agree to abide by our terms and conditions and any applicable laws and regulations.
- **The prices and commission rates on this website are subject to change without notice.**</content>
	<excerpt>Help businesses and earn extra cash.
Contact us today to learn more!</excerpt>
	<description>Are you looking to make some extra cash while helping out businesses in need of digital solutions? Look no further than Phixel's Referral Rewards Program. Commission rates from 5% to 15% of project value. Contact us today to learn more!

Our team of experienced designers and developers provides personalized digital solutions for businesses of all sizes. And with our referral program, you can earn commission just by referring clients to us.</description>
	<media>
		<url type="jpg">media/6a642218/referral-cover.jpg</url>
		<url type="mp3">media/b4b99b2c/racing-hearts.mp3</url>
		<url type="mp3">media/243db555/referal-mix.es_.mp3</url>
		<url type="mp3">media/ff49e1b7/referal-robot.es_.mp3</url>
		<url type="mp3">media/55f86538/referal.es_.mp3</url>
		<url type="jpg">media/15be34b0/referral-landed.jpg</url>
		<url type="jpg">media/54dc5587/referral-lunch.jpg</url>
		<url type="jpg">media/25aa22cd/referral-relax.jpg</url>
		<url type="jpg">media/eff47e30/referral-robot.jpg</url>
		<url type="mp4">media/14b4baf7/referral.es_.mp4</url>
		<url type="jpg">media/31b5e16d/cover-referrals.jpg</url>
	</media>
	<info>
		<slug>referral</slug>
		<date>01/04/2023</date>
		<url>https://phixel.net/en/referral/</url>
		<category>Page</category>
		<url>page</url>
		<emojis>💰💻👔📈📊👥💡🤝👍📱</emojis>
		<hashtags>
			<hashtag>ReferralRewards</hashtag>
			<hashtag>EarnExtraCash</hashtag>
			<hashtag>CommissionProgram</hashtag>
			<hashtag>DigitalSolutions</hashtag>
			<hashtag>BusinessDevelopment</hashtag>
			<hashtag>DesignServices</hashtag>
			<hashtag>Marketing</hashtag>
			<hashtag>Opportunity</hashtag>
			<hashtag>EarningPotential</hashtag>
			<hashtag>PhixelSolutions</hashtag>
		</hashtags>
		<tags>
			<tag>Referral Rewards Program</tag>
			<tag>Commission Rates</tag>
			<tag>Digital Solutions</tag>
			<tag>Business Growth</tag>
			<tag>Program Tiers</tag>
		</tags>
	</info>
</item>
